bmwhk.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy

Effective date: 31 May 2013

1\. Our commitment to protect your privacy  
    1.1 BMW Concessionaires (HK) Ltd. ("BMW HK", "we", "our" or "us") appreciates your interest in us and our products and services. Your privacy is important to us and we wish to explain our privacy policy so that you may feel comfortable visiting our website (www.bmwhk.com) and using our products and services. By visiting our website and any of its pages, you agree to the terms described in this policy.

2\. Personal data we collect  
    2.1 We collect and store information you enter on our website or give us in any other way, including when you purchase a product from us or use our services, contact our Showrooms or Service Centres, or through car shows, contests and promotions. Such information may comprise personal data as defined under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance as amended from time to time ("Data") and include but not limited to:  
        2.1.1 Your personal information such as your name, age group, phone number, email and/or address; and  
        2.1.2 Your credit or debit card information and billing information, including name of cardholder, card number, expiry date and billing address.  
        2.1.3 Certain Data (particularly relating to your contact information) are required for specific services and if you fail to supply such Data, we may be unable to provide the services in full.  
    2.2 We do not intend to collect information from minors. However, as we cannot distinguish the age of persons who access our website, our privacy policy applies to all who access our website. If a child has provided us with Data without the consent of his parent or guardian, the parent or guardian should contact us (please see section 11 for details) to request the removal of the information. 

3\. Purposes for Collection and Use of Data  
    3.1 The Data provided by you will be used by us for the purpose for which it was requested, and for directly related purposes as follows:   
        3.1.1 Application, administration, continuation and termination of the use of our products or services;  
        3.1.2 Processing billing and payment, maintaining a credit history, determining amounts outstanding and if necessary, collection of outstanding payments;  
        3.1.3 Considering or fulfilling requests or application of any nature submitted by you, whether online, over the phone or through other channels;  
        3.1.4 Handling and following up service calls, enquiries and complaints;  
        3.1.5 Verification of your identity;  
        3.1.6 Administering contests and sweepstakes conducted by us, including disclosing the winner of any such contests;  
        3.1.7 Enforcement of any contract entered into between you and BMW HK;  
        3.1.8 Updating and enhancing our records;  
        3.1.9 Meeting the requirements to make disclosure to any governmental, legal or regulatory authority in Hong Kong under the requirements of any law binding on us; and  
        3.1.10 Enabling us to better understand the demographics of our customers and provide products/services better tailored to your needs.  
    3.2 We will collect and submit as applicable a copy of your Hong Kong Identity Card ("HKIC") to the Transport Department of The Government of the HKSAR for vehicle registration and licensing purposes, and to insurance company for insurance arrangements. We will also request your HKIC number / Hong Kong Driving License number for identity verification purposes for test drive arrangements but not for any other purposes.

4\. Information Captured Automatically  
    4.1 Like many websites, we automatically receive certain types of information when your web browser accesses our website, including your IP address, browser type, operating system, pages you visit on our website, which website you came from or go to and the date and length of your visit. We may use and evaluate such information for the purposes of website administration and understanding our customers better.

5\. Use of Data in Direct Marketing  
    5.1 We intend to use your Data in direct marketing, and we may not so use your Data unless we have received your consent (which includes an indication of no objection).  
    5.2 We intend to use your Data including your name, phone number, email and/or address to contact you about the following:  
        5.2.1 products, services and promotional events of BMW HK, BMW AG and Sime Darby Motor Group;  
        5.2.2 banking services offered by our business partners as part of the comprehensive service we strive to provide our customers.  
    5.3 We will not disclose your Data to any third parties for direct marketing purposes without your consent.  
    5.4 Should you not want us to use your Data for direct marketing, please let us know via any one of the free response channels in section 11. You can also choose not to receive such marketing materials by selecting the unsubscribe option which we provide in each email, sms or mms sent to you, or otherwise inform us.

6\. Disclosure and Transfer of Data  
    6.1 We do not sell or trade your Data with third parties and we strive to protect your privacy. Your Data may however be transferred within or outside Hong Kong as follows (if applicable):   
        6.1.1 other companies (including branch offices, subsidiaries, holding companies, associated companies or affiliates) within our group of companies;   
        6.1.2 governmental, legal or regulatory authority in Hong Kong;   
        6.1.3 our legal and financial advisers;  
        6.1.4 third party service providers engaged by us to assist with debt collection and customer services;   
        6.1.5 insurance company for the application of car insurance;  
        6.1.6 credit information, reference bureau or financial service company for the application of financial services; and  
        6.1.7 our assigns or successor in title.

7\. Security and Accuracy of Data  
    7.1 Except as mentioned in section 6 above, your Data, however stored, will be accessed by our employees or service providers who are authorized to do so.   
    7.2 Where Data is stored electronically, it will be kept password-protected in the BMW HK computing facilities (including servers and back-up tapes), and accessible only by authorized personnel of BMW HK or service providers. Data encryption will be applied where appropriate.  
    7.3 Employees and service providers designated to handle Data will be instructed to do so only in accordance with this privacy policy.  
    7.4 We shall take reasonable steps to keep your Data as accurate, complete, and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used. Data that is used on an ongoing basis, including information that is disclosed to third parties (please see section 6 for details), will generally be kept accurate and up-to-date. You can update or correct the Data held by us in accordance with section 11. 

8\. Retention of Data8.1 Data provided by you is retained if the purpose for which the Data was collected still exists, it is so required by law, statue or regulation, or it is in the public interest. Data will be destroyed once its requirement is ended. 

9\. Cookies   
    9.1 When you access our website, we store information about your visit in a small text file called a "cookie" on your hard disk. This helps us to identify you and remember your preferences the next time you visit us.   
    9.2 Only information that you have provided will be stored in the cookie, and only the website which created the cookie can read it. This does not allow it access to the rest of the computer.   
    9.3 You can configure your Internet browser not to accept cookies, or to alert you every time a cookie is offered, letting you decide whether or not to accept it. However, some features of our website may not be available if you prevent the use of cookies. 

10\. Third party websites  
    10.1 Our privacy policy does not extend to third-party websites that may be linked from our website, or from any other broadcast affiliated with us.

11\. Data Access and Correction  
    11.1 You may at any time request access to or update/correct your Data held by us. You may also ask us to delete you or your Data from any active mailing or distribution list.  
    11.2 To exercise any of your rights above, please visit www.bmwhk.com/unsubscribe to unsubscribe.

12\. Amendments to Privacy Policy   
    12.1 We may revise this privacy policy from time to time by updating this version. Therefore, please visit our website from time to time to determine any changes to these terms.
